Art Collins Collection ARC.0001
Library and Archives
- Series VII: Audiovisual Materials [RESTRICTED], 1966-2005 and undated
  Some of the audiovisual materials in this series are on defunct media formats and, therefore, are RESTRICTED. Access copies of these materials will have to be created prior to use. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available.
  Divided into 4 subseries: ¾-inch videocassettes, videotapes, audiocassettes, and test pressings. Each subseries consists of materials relating to Collins’ clients, as well as other artists in the industry. The files are arranged alphabetically by artist and/or title and then chronologically.
  - Subseries 1: 3/4” Videocassettes [RESTRICTED], 1981-93 and undated
    The audiovisual materials in this subseries are on defunct media formats and, therefore, are RESTRICTED. Access copies of these materials will have to be created prior to use. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available.
    - Dead Boys video, Martin Abrams Films Inc., 1980 (Box 41, Object 1)
    - Kinks, The: One for the Road, 1980 (Box 41, Object 2)
    - Letterman, David "Franken and Davis", 1983 March 17 (Box 41, Object 3)
    - Nugent, Ted music videos, 1992 August 6 (Box 41, Object 4)
    - Pop, Iggy “Cold Metal” music video (Box 41, Object 5)
    - Pop, Iggy “One More” music video, 1993 (Box 41, Object 6)
    - Pop, Iggy "Beside You" music video, undated (Box 41, Object 7)
    - Pop, Iggy "Cry for Love" final edit, 1986 (Box 41, Object 8)
    - Pop, Iggy (3 copies), undated (Box 41, Object 9)
    - Portrait of a Legend: Jerry Lee Lewis, 1981 (Box 42, Object 1)
    - Portrait of a Legend: Kenny Rogers, 1981 (Box 42, Object 2)
    - Portrait of a Legend: Little Richard, 1981 (Box 42, Object 3)
    - Portrait of a Legend: Smokey Robinson, 1981 (Box 42, Object 4)
    - Portrait of a Legend: Stevie Wonder, 1981 (Box 42, Object 5)
    - White Zombie " Black Sunshine" music video, 1992 August 8 (Box 42, Object 6)
  - Subseries 2: Videotapes, 1968-1999 and undated
    Seperated Materials
    Additional videotapes have been transferred to the library collection. Please search for the "Art Collins Collection" in the library catalog for a list of donated titles.
    - 120 Minutes, undated (Box 43, Object 1)
    - Adventures of Pete and Pete, undated (Box 43, Object 2)
    - America’ s Wildest Home Video Contest (1st place winner), undated (Box 43, Object 3)
    - Crosby, Stills, Nash & Young “Live at Wembley Arena and Winterland (Box 43, Object 4)
    - Home to Rent, undated (Box 43, Object 5)
    - IggFest Much Music, 1993 October 7 (Box 43, Object 6)
    - Images Censorship Segment, undated (Box 43, Object 7)
    - Influences MTV On Air Promos, undated (Box 43, Object 8)
    - International Presentation, 1995 (Box 43, Object 9)
    - Jagger, Mick "I Want My MTV" ad spots, 1982 June 22 (Box 43, Object 10)
    - Jagger, Mick “Private Reel Pt. 1” (NBC), undated (Box 43, Object 11)
    - Jagger, Mick “Private Reel Pt. 2” (NBC), undated (Box 43, Object 12)
    - Jagger, Mick “Private Reel” (unedited), undated (Box 43, Object 13)
    - Jagger, Mick: speaks to WEA and EMI records, 1981 July (Box 43, Object 14)
    - Jagger, Mick: interview (NBC), undated (Box 43, Object 15)
    - Keith Richards and the Expensive Wino “Live at the Hollywood Palladium”, December 1988 (Box 43, Object 16)
    - Live at Woodstock, 1969 (Box 43, Object 17)
    - Mitchell, Joni: PBS American Masters Series, undated (Box 43, Object 18)
    - MTV Extra Stones Special, undated (Box 43, Object 19)
    - MTV Paris interviews, 1982 July (Box 43, Object 20)
    - Much Music, undated (Box 43, Object 21)
    - Nirvana “Unplugged”, undated (Box 43, Object 22)
    - Iggy Pop music videos (Box 44, Object 1-23)
    - Richards, Keith “Private Reel Pt. 1 and Pt. 2”, undated (Box 45, Object 1)
    - Rolling Stones concert footage (Box 45, Object 2-24)
    - Rolling Stones music videos (Box 46, Object 1-18)
    - Rolling Stones television clips (Box 46, Object 19-22)
    - The Manson Family, 1990 (Box 46, Object 23)
    - To Belong, undated (Box 46, Object 24)
    - Van Morrison “Live at the Orphanage 1972 and Live in London 1973” (Box 46, Object 25)
    - VH1 Fashion Awards, 1998 (Box 46, Object 26)
    - Video Reels, undated (Box 46, Object 27)
    - Year of the Horse, undated (Box 46, Object 28)
  - Subseries 3: Audiocassettes, 1978 and undated
    Additional audiocassettes have been transferred to the library collection. Please search for the "Art Collins Collection" in the library catalog for a list of donated titles.
    - Keith’s Tape “X-Mas Issue”, undated (Box 46, Object 1)
    - Rocket 88 Live at Montreaux, undated (Box 46, Object 2-3)
    - Rolling Stones mixed tapes, undated (Box 46, Object 4-9)
    - Stu's Boogie Woogie Bad Boy Blues Collectables, undated (Box 46, Object 10)
    - Stewart, Ian, undated (Box 46, Object 11)
  - Subseries 4: Test Pressings, 1983-1984 and undated
    - The Cars, 1984 February 21 (Box 47, Object 1)
    - Pop, Iggy, A&M Records, 1986 August 19 (Box 47, Object 2)
    - Rolling Stones, "Feel on Baby", undated (Box 47, Object 3)
    - Rolling Stones, "Fool to Cry", undated (Box 47, Object 4)
    - Rolling Stones, "She Was Hot", undated (Box 47, Object 5)
    - Rolling Stones, "Think I'm Going Mad", undated (Box 47, Object 6)
    - Rolling Stones, "Too Much Blood", undated (Box 47, Object 7)
    - Rolling Stones: ABC Spotlight Special, 1984 March 18 (Box 47, Object 8)
    - Rolling Stones: Sterling Sound, 1984 April 26 (Box 47, Object 9)
    - Tosh, Peter, undated (Box 47, Object 10)
    - Tosh, Peter, Stetling Sounds, 1981 June 26 (Box 47, Object 11)
    - Townsend, Pete, 1983 September 14 (Box 47, Object 12)
    - Un-labeled test pressings, undated (Box 47, Object 13-17)
- Series VIII: Printed Materials, 1963-2003 and undated
  Divided into three subseries: periodicals, newspapers, and film scripts. The periodical and newspaper subseries contain various articles about Collins’ clients, as well as major events in music history. The film scripts include original scripts that were sent to Collins’ clients. The items are arranged alphabetically by title and/or author within the subseries and then chronologically.
  Books and sheet music books have been transferred to the library collection. Please search for the "Art Collins Papers" in the library catalog for a list of donated titles.
  - Subseries 1: Periodicals, 1972-2003 and undated
    Additional periodicals have been transferred to the library collection. Please search for the "Art Collins Collection" in the library catalog for a list of donated titles.
    - A Tribute to John Lennon and The Beatles, 1980 (Box 48, Object 1)
    - Alfred's Basic Guitar Method, Alfred D'Auberge and Morton Manus (Box 48, Object 2)
    - Cashbox, 1982 July 3 (Box 48, Object 3)
    - Celebrity, 1977 September (Box 48, Object 4)
    - Circus, 1975 August (Box 48, Object 5)
    - Circus, 1976 June1 (Box 48, Object 6)
    - Esquire, 1985 May (Box 48, Object 7)
    - Event, 1981 June (Box 48, Object 8)
    - Globe Special - Where Are They Now?, 1993 (Box 48, Object 9)
    - Guitar Player, 1977 November (Box 48, Object 10)
    - Hit Parader, 1977 December (Box 48, Object 11)
    - Hit Parader, 1981 November (Box 48, Object 12)
    - International Musician, 1981 December (Box 48, Object 13)
    - John Lennon Tribute, 1980 December (Box 48, Object 15)
    - John Lennon: A Personal Pictorial Diary, Sportomatic Special Editions, undated (Box 48, Object 16)
    - John Lennon: All You Need is Love, undated (Box 48, Object 17)
    - Life Magazine, 1981 November (Box 48, Object 18)
    - Mad Australian, undated (Box 48, Object 19)
    - Men's Fitness, 1999 August (Box 48, Object 20)
    - Modern Hi-Fi Stereo and Guide, 1971 June (Box 48, Object 21)
    - Moviegoer, 1982 September (Box 48, Object 22)
    - Newsweek, 1980 December 22 (Box 48, Object 23)
    - Newsweek, 1987 August 3 (Box 48, Object 24)
    - Newsweek, 1995 October 23 (Box 48, Object 25)
    - Newsweek, 1997 June 2 (Box 48, Object 26)
    - Newsweek, 1997 October 6 (Box 48, Object 27)
    - On Stage Magazine, 1981 November (Box 48, Object 28)
    - People Weekly, 1977 November 7 (Box 48, Object 29)
    - People Weekly, 1977 December 12 (Box 48, Object 30)
    - People Weekly, 1980 December 22 (Box 48, Object 31)
    - People Weekly, 1981 June 22 (Box 48, Object 32)
    - People Weekly, 1981 October 12 (Box 48, Object 33)
    - People Weekly, 1982 March 22 (Box 48, Object 34)
    - People Weekly, 1984 June 11 (Box 48, Object 35)
    - People Weekly, 1985 July 29 (Box 48, Object 36)
    - People Weekly, 1985 September 16 (Box 48, Object 37)
    - People Weekly, 1987 February 17 (Box 48, Object 38)
    - People Weekly, 1987 August 9 (Box 48, Object 39)
    - People Weekly, 1989 March 28 (Box 48, Object 40)
    - People Weekly, 1989 August 6 (Box 48, Object 41)
    - People Weekly, 1994 April 25 (Box 48, Object 42)
    - People Weekly, 1994 August 15 (Box 48, Object 43)
    - People Weekly, 1995 August 21 (Box 48, Object 44)
    - Philly Weekly, 1981 September 23 (Box 48, Object 45)
    - Pictures from the Mojo Wall of Sound (Box 48, Object 46)
    - Press Releases and Comic Strip, undated (Box 48, Object 47)
    - Pulse, 1993 August (Box 48, Object 48)
    - Punk Planet - Notes From Underground, 2003 May (Box 48, Object 49)
    - Punk Planet - Notes From Underground, 2003 July (Box 48, Object 50)
    - The Beatles: Band of the Century Special Issue (Box 48, Object 51)
    - Record Review, 1977 November (Box 48, Object 52)
    - Record Review, 1978 October (Box 48, Object 53)
    - Relix, 1978 August (Box 48, Object 54)
    - Rock and Folk Magazine, 1980 (Box 48, Object 55)
    - Rocky Mountain Hi-Note, 1981 October (Box 48, Object 56)
    - Spin, 1994 September (Box 48, Object 57)
    - Sunday Review, 1972 August 12 (Box 48, Object 58)
    - The Death and Life of John Lennon by Pete Hamill, 1980 December 22 (Box 48, Object 59)
    - Record Magazine, 1981 January (Box 48, Object 60)
    - Time Magazine, 1965 May 21 (Box 48, Object 61)
    - Time Magazine, 1980 December 22 (Box 48, Object 62)
    - Time Magazine, 1981 September 7 (Box 48, Object 63)
    - Time Magazine, 1988 January 11 (Box 48, Object 64)
    - Time Magazine, 1989 Fall (Box 48, Object 65)
    - Time Magazine, 1989 September 4 (Box 48, Object 66)
    - Time Magazine, 1998 June 8 (Box 48, Object 67)
    - Time Out New York, 1999 February 18 (Box 48, Object 68)
    - Timeout Magazine, 1982 June (Box 48, Object 69)
    - Trans-Oceanic Trouser Press, 1975 June (Box 48, Object 70)
    - Trouser Press, 1978 June (Box 48, Object 71)
    - Tuned In San Diego, 1981 October 3 (Box 48, Object 72)
    - TV Guide, 1981 November 21 (Box 48, Object 73)
    - US Magazine, 1981 March 17 (Box 48, Object 74)
    - US Magazine, 1981 November 10 (Box 48, Object 75)
    - Vanity Fair, 2000 November (Box 48, Object 76)
    - What's On in London, 1982 July 1 (Box 48, Object 77)
    - Wings Fan Club, 1981 (Box 48, Object 78)
    - John Lennon and the Beatles Special Tribute, 1980 (Box 48, Object 14)
  - Subseries 2: Newspapers, 1963-1999 and undated
    - Aquarian Weekly, 1978 June 28 (Box 49, Object 1)
    - Aquarian Weekly, 1981 September 9 (Box 49, Object 2)
    - Aquarian Weekly, 1981 November 18 (Box 49, Object 3)
    - Aquarian, 1981 May 13 (Box 49, Object 4)
    - Aquarian, 1981 May 6 (Box 49, Object 5)
    - Atlanta Constitution, 1981 October 26 (Box 49, Object 6)
    - Black Book, 1997 June (Box 49, Object 7)
    - Black Book, 1999 December (Box 49, Object 8)
    - Boston Globe, 1974 August 4 (Box 49, Object 9)
    - Bulletin, 1981 September 26 (Box 49, Object 10)
    - Bulletin, 1981 September 27 (Box 49, Object 11)
    - Chicago Tribune, 1978 July 9 (Box 49, Object 12)
    - Chicago Tribune, 1981 November 23 (Box 49, Object 13)
    - Chicago Tribune, 1981 November 23 (Box 49, Object 14)
    - Chicago Tribune, 1981 November 24 (Box 49, Object 15)
    - Cincinnati Enquirer, 1978 July 9 (Box 49, Object 16)
    - Commercial Appeal (Memphis, TN), 1977 August 17 (Box 49, Object 17)
    - Daily Express (Britain), 1982 June 30 (Box 49, Object 18)
    - Daily Herald (Chicago), 1981 November 22 (Box 49, Object 19)
    - Daily Herald (Chicago), 1981 November 23 (Box 49, Object 20)
    - Daily Herald (Chicago), 1981 November 24 (Box 49, Object 21)
    - Daily Mirror (Britain), 1982 June 30 (Box 49, Object 22)
    - Daily News, 1972 July 24 (Box 49, Object 23)
    - Daily News, 1981 September 26 (Box 49, Object 24)
    - Daily News, 1982 May 16 (Box 49, Object 25)
    - Daily Telegraph (London), 1982 June 25 (Box 49, Object 26)
    - Daily Telegraph (London), 1982 June 26 (Box 49, Object 27)
    - Dallas Morning News, 1978 July 19 (Box 49, Object 28)
    - Dallas Morning News, 1981 October 31 (Box 49, Object 29)
    - Dallas Morning News, 1981 November 1 (Box 49, Object 30)
    - Dallas Times Herald, 1978 July 19 (Box 49, Object 31)
    - Dallas Times Herald, 1981 October 30 (Box 49, Object 32)
    - Dallas Times Herald, 1981 October 31 (Box 49, Object 33)
    - Dallas Times Herald, 1981 November 1 (Box 49, Object 34)
    - Dallas Times Herald, 1984 December 1 (Box 49, Object 35)
    - Denver Post, 1982 October 2 (Box 49, Object 36)
    - Discoveries, 1998 June (Box 50, Object 1)
    - Discoveries, 1999 August (Box 50, Object 2)
    - Discoveries, 2000 May (Box 50, Object 3)
    - Entertainment Magazine, Woodstock Special Edition, 1994 (Box 50, Object 4)
    - European Music Awards program, 1999 (Box 50, Object 5)
    - Flexipop, undated (Box 50, Object 6)
    - Globe and Mail (Toronto), 1979 April 23 (Box 50, Object 7)
    - Goldmine, 1995 March 17 (Box 50, Object 8)
    - Goldmine, 1997 March 28 (Box 50, Object 9)
    - Friday Evening, 1981 October 30 (Box 50, Object 10)
    - Good Morning (Buffalo), 1981 September 27 (Box 50, Object 11)
    - Grammy Awards Book (past winners) (Box 50, Object 12)
    - Hartford Courant, 1963 November 26 (Box 50, Object 13)
    - Hartford Courant, 1974 August 9 (Box 50, Object 14)
    - Hartford Courant, 1981 November 10 (Box 50, Object 15)
    - Hartford Times, 1963 November 25 (Box 50, Object 16)
    - L.A. Weekly, 1981 October 16 (Box 50, Object 17)
    - Los Angeles Herald Examiner, 1978 July 25 (Box 50, Object 18)
    - Los Angeles Herald Examiner, 1981 October 5 (Box 50, Object 19)
    - Los Angeles Herald Examiner, 1981 October 8 (Box 50, Object 20)
    - Los Angeles Herald Examiner, 1981 October 7 (Box 50, Object 21)
    - Los Angeles Times, 1978 July 25 (Box 50, Object 22)
    - Los Angeles Times, 1978 June 10 (Box 50, Object 23)
    - Memphis Press-Scimitar, 1977 August 17 (Box 51, Object 1)
    - Music Connection, 1995 January 22 (Box 51, Object 2)
    - Music Express (Canada), 1981 (Box 51, Object 3)
    - Music Gig, 1976 June (Box 51, Object 4)
    - Music News, 1977 September (Box 51, Object 5)
    - Music News, 1978 June (Box 51, Object 6)
    - Music Sound Output, 1986 April (Box 51, Object 7)
    - New Musical Express, 1978 October 14 (Box 51, Object 8)
    - New Musical Express, 1979 March 17 (Box 51, Object 9)
    - New Musical Express, 1979 May 26 (Box 51, Object 10)
    - New York Daily News, 1981 November 8 (Box 51, Object 11)
    - New York Newsday, 1990 March 5 (Box 51, Object 12)
    - New York Post, 1979 September 21 (Box 51, Object 13)
    - New York Post, 1979 December 4 (Box 51, Object 14)
    - New York Post, 1980 August 1 (Box 51, Object 15)
    - New York Post, 1981 October 21 (Box 51, Object 16)
    - New York Post, 1981 October 29 (Box 51, Object 17)
    - New York Post, 1981 November 5 (Box 51, Object 18)
    - New York Post, 1981 November 6 (Box 51, Object 19)
    - New York Post, 1981 November 10 (Box 51, Object 20)
    - New York Post, 1981 November 16 (Box 51, Object 21)
    - New York Post, 1981 November 20 (Box 51, Object 22)
    - New York Post, 1983 January 20 (Box 51, Object 23)
    - New York Post, 1983 November 28 (Box 51, Object 24)
    - New York Post, 1983 December 29 (Box 51, Object 25)
    - New York Post, 1984 April 2 (Box 51, Object 26)
    - New York Post, 1985 October 2 (Box 51, Object 27)
    - New York Post, 1986 January 1 (Box 51, Object 28)
    - New York Post, 1986 January 28 (Box 51, Object 29)
    - New York Post, 1990 July 31 (Box 51, Object 30)
    - New York Post, 1990 August 28 (Box 51, Object 31)
    - New York Post, 1994 April 10 (Box 51, Object 32)
    - New York Post, 1996 September 19 (Box 51, Object 33)
    - New York Post, 1998 April 20 (Box 51, Object 34)
    - New York Sunday News Magazine, 1980 September 28 (Box 52, Object 1)
    - New York Sunday News Magazine, 1981 November 8 (Box 52, Object 2)
    - New York Times, 1974 August 9 (Box 52, Object 3)
    - New York Times, 1975 January 2 (Box 52, Object 4)
    - New York Times, 1981 December 27 (Box 52, Object 5)
    - New York Times, 1983 February 6 (Box 52, Object 6)
    - New York Times, 1983 February 11 (Box 52, Object 7)
    - News of the World (Great Britain), 1984 January 15 (Box 52, Object 8)
    - Night Owl (New York), 1981 September 2 (Box 52, Object 9)
    - Not the New York Times, 1978 October 3 (Box 52, Object 10)
    - Oakland Tribune, 1978 July 27 (Box 52, Object 11)
    - Philadelphia Daily News, 1981 September 26 (Box 52, Object 12)
    - Post-Standard (Syracuse), 1981 November 27 (Box 52, Object 13)
    - Post-Standard (Syracuse), 1981 November 26 (Box 52, Object 14)
    - Rocky Mountain News, 1978 July 17 (Box 52, Object 15)
    - Rocky Mountain News, 1981 October 2 (Box 52, Object 16)
    - San Francisco Chronicle, 1978 July 22 (Box 52, Object 17)
    - San Francisco Chronicle, 1981 October 17 (Box 52, Object 18)
    - San Francisco Chronicle, 1981 October 19 (Box 52, Object 19)
    - San Francisco Examiner, 1978 July 25 (Box 52, Object 20)
    - San Francisco Examiner, 1981 October 16 (Box 52, Object 21)
    - San Francisco Examiner, 1981 October 18 (Box 52, Object 22)
    - Sentinel Star, 1981 October 26 (Box 52, Object 23)
    - Soho Weekly News, 1978 June 22 (Box 53, Object 1)
    - Soho Weekly News, 1981 November 4 (Box 53, Object 2)
    - Standard (London), 1982 June 28 (Box 53, Object 3)
    - Standard (London), 1982 July 29 (Box 53, Object 4)
    - Standard (London), 1983 June 29 (Box 53, Object 5)
    - Star, 1985 August 25 (Box 53, Object 6)
    - Sun (Britain), 1982 June 29 (Box 53, Object 7)
    - Sun (Britain), 1982 June 30 (Box 53, Object 8)
    - Sun-Times (Chicago), 1978 July 7 (Box 53, Object 9)
    - Sun-Times (Chicago), 1981 November 25 (Box 53, Object 10)
    - Sun-Times (Chicago), 1981 November 26 (Box 53, Object 11)
    - Syracuse Herald Journal, 1981 November 27 (Box 53, Object 12)
    - Syracuse Herald Journal, 1981 November 28 (Box 53, Object 13)
    - Times (Britain), 1981 December 4 (Box 53, Object 15)
    - Times (Britain), 1981 December 5 (Box 53, Object 16)
    - Times (Britain), 1982 June 9 (Box 53, Object 17)
    - Times–Picayune, 1981 December 4 (Box 53, Object 14)
    - Today (Gannett Newspaper), 1981 November 6 (Box 53, Object 18)
    - Toronto Star, 1979 April 21 (Box 53, Object 19)
    - Toronto Star, 1979 April 22 (Box 53, Object 20)
    - Toronto Star, 1979 April 23 (Box 53, Object 21)
    - Toronto Sun, 1979 April 23 (Box 53, Object 22)
    - Triad (Chicago), 1978 July (Box 53, Object 23)
    - USA Today, 1983 November 10 (Box 53, Object 24)
    - Variety, 1981 December 23 (Box 53, Object 25)
    - Village Voice, 1974 August 23 (Box 53, Object 26)
    - Village Voice, 1997 April 15 (Box 53, Object 27)
    - Virginian Pilot, 1981 December 19 (Box 53, Object 28)
    - Vox, 1998 January (Box 53, Object 29)
    - Washington Post, 1981 December 8 (Box 53, Object 30)
    - Washington Post, 1981 December 9 (Box 53, Object 31)
    - Washington Post, 1981 December 10 (Box 53, Object 32)
    - Washington Post, 1981 December 11 (Box 53, Object 33)
    - Washington Post, 1983 November 10 (Box 53, Object 34)
    - Weekly Soho News, 1978 October 19 (Box 53, Object 35)
    - Weekly Soho News, 1979 February 8 (Box 53, Object 36)
    - Zoo World, 1974 June 4 (Box 53, Object 37)
    - Zoo World, 1974 August 15 (Box 53, Object 38)
    - Zoo World, 1974 September 26 (Box 53, Object 39)
    - Various articles, undated (Box 53, Object 40-41)
  - Subseries 3: Film Scripts, 1990-2002 and undated
    - Antle, Spencer. The Escapist., undated (Box 54, Object 1)
    - The Asshole., undated (Box 54, Object 2)
    - Batali, Dean. The Adventures of Pete and Pete., 1995 (Box 54, Object 3)
    - Behr, Melissa and Sherrie Rose. Me and Will., 1996 (Box 54, Object 4)
    - De Luca, Michael. Freddy's Dead: The Final Nightmare., 1990 (Box 54, Object 5)
    - DeJoseph, Dominic. Tarred and Feathered., 1994 (Box 54, Object 6)
    - Depp, Johnny. The Brave., 1996 (Box 54, Object 7)
    - Donnhofer, Deigo. The Virgin., 1994 (Box 54, Object 8)
    - Feuer, Stuart and Laurent Rejito. Country Heritage., 1996 (Box 54, Object 9)
    - Gilligan, Vince. Home Fries., 1993 (Box 54, Object 10)
    - Goyer, David S. The Crow: City of Angels., 1995 (Box 54, Object 11)
    - Hodge, John. Trainspotting., 1995 (Box 54, Object 12)
    - Levy, Jefrey. Et, Tu Babe., undated (Box 54, Object 13)
    - Lovedog, Cheri. Prey for Rock and Roll., 2002 (Box 54, Object 14)
    - Mahon, Maureen. The Thirteenth Floor., 1996 (Box 54, Object 15)
    - Roisentul, Gary J. Regards from Hell., 1996 (Box 54, Object 16)
    - Ransom., 1995 (Box 54, Object 17)
    - Rose, Dan. Wayne County Ramblin., 1992 (Box 54, Object 18)
    - Sarafian, Tedi. Tank Girl., 1993 (Box 54, Object 19)
    - Soodik, Trish. Shake, Rattle and Rock., 1994 (Box 54, Object 20)
- Series IX: Rolling Stones Photograph, 1984
  Contains a large photograph of Mick Jagger performing live on stage.
  - Mick Jagger on stage, undated (Box 55, Object 1)